// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The type of listening skills that can enable you to master what the speaker is saying is _______",
    answer: "Listening for interpretation and critical evaluation",
    options: [
      "Class listening",
      "Listening for specific information",
      "Listening for interpretation and critical evaluation",
      "General listening"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In listening comprehension, the most important thing a listener should determine is the _______",
    answer: "Main idea of the speech event",
    options: [
      "Learning of everything mentioned",
      "Main idea of the speech event",
      "Supporting detail of lectures",
      "Study of one's notes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The sentence “APC governed states are not ready for a change in government” is an example of _______",
    answer: "opinion",
    options: [
      "fact",
      "fable",
      "fallacy",
      "opinion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Vital information that reveal truth or reality are called _______",
    answer: "facts",
    options: [
      "fiction",
      "facts",
      "fallacies",
      "assumptions"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The art of receiving information from stored information in the multi-media system is called _______",
    answer: "retrieval",
    options: [
      "retrieval",
      "adaptation",
      "storage",
      "reception"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following may not help the listener who is trying to take notes from a lecture _______",
    answer: "Use of passages",
    options: [
      "Use of abbreviations",
      "Putting down summary of main points",
      "Understanding what a speaker says",
      "Use of passages"
    ]
  },
 
  
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "During study time, the activity of jotting down notes from textbooks, journals or study text is called _______",
    answer: "note-making",
    options: [
      "note-writing",
      "note-usage",
      "note-making",
      "note-taking"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When we listen to lectures or speeches and jot down important points, we are performing _______",
    answer: "note-taking",
    options: [
      "note-taking",
      "note-making",
      "note-forming",
      "drafting"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Comprehension basically means _______",
    answer: "understanding",
    options: [
      "assistance",
      "hearing",
      "understanding",
      "development"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "All but one of these affects comprehension _______",
    answer: "rate of breathing",
    options: [
      "unfamiliarity with the topic",
      "rate of breathing",
      "inability to think deeply",
      "lack of interest"
    ]
  },
];

